Guide to the Collected editions of standard authors, ca. 1829-1903.
Collected editions of standard authors
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; The Dolliver Romance; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. XI (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Tales, Sketches, and Other Papers; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. XII (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Doctor Grimshawe’s Secret; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1882; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. XIII (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Julian; Nathaniel hawthorne and His Wife Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1884; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. XIV (Box 16)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1771-1797; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. I (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1798-1806; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. II (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1806-1812; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. III (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1812-1814; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. IV (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1814-1818; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. V (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1818-1821; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. VI (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1822-1825; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. VII (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1825-1826; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. VIII (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1826-1830; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. IX (Box 17)
- Lockhart, J.G.; Memoirs of the Life or Sir Walter Scott, Bart 1831-1832; Robert Cadell; Edinbrgh; 1839; Life of Sir Walter Scott, Bart Vol. X (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Abbot Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XX (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Abbot Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Kenilworth Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Kenilworth Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXIII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Pirate Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXIV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Pirate Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Fortunes of Nigel Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXVI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Fortunes of Nigel Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXVII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Peveril of the Peak Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXVIII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Peveril of the Peak Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXIX (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Peveril of the Peak Vol. III; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXX (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Quentin Durward Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Quentin Durward Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; St. Ronan’s Well Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXIII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; St. Ronan’s Well Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXIV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Redgauntlt Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Redgauntlt Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXVI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Betrothed; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXVII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Talisman; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXVIII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Woodstock Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XXXIX (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Woodstock Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XL (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; The Highland Widow; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Fair Maid of Perth Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Fair Maid of Perth Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLIII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Anne of Geierstein Vol. I; Robert Cadell & Company; 1833; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLIV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Anne of Geierstein Vol. II; Robert Cadell & Company; 1833; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLV (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Count Robert of Paris; Robert Cadell & Company; 1833; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLVI (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart; Castle Dangerous; Robert Cadell & Company; 1833; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLVII (Box 17)
- Scott, Sir Walter, The Surgeon’s Daughter; Robert Cadell & Company; 1833; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XLVIII (Box 17)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Lionel Lincoln; D. Appleton and Company; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Chainbearer; D. Appleton and Company; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Mercedes of Castle; D. Appleton and Company; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Sea-Lions; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Water-Witch; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Pathfinder; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Wyandotte; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Heidenmaurer; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Prairie; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Wept of Wish-Ton-Wish; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Satanstoe; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Pilot; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Pioneers; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Headsman; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Home as Found; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Deerslayer; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; Precaution; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Two Admirals; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Crater; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Cooper, J. Fenimore; The Redskins; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 18)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Twenty Years After Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Twenty Years After Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Queen’s Necklace Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Queen’s Necklace Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Two Dianas Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Two Dianas Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Vicomte de Bragelonne Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Vicomte de Bragelonne Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Vicomte de Bragelonne Vol. III; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Olympe de Cleves Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Olympe de Cleves Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Count of Monte Cristo Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Count of Monte Cristo Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Count of Monte Cristo Vol. III; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; La Comtesse de Charny Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; La Comtesse de Charny Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The She-Wolves of Machecoul Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 19)
- Macaulay, Lord; The History of Emgland: From the Accession of James the Second Vol. V; Harper & Brothers; New York; 1879 (Box 19)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. II; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1895 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. III; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1895 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. IV; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1895 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. V; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. VI; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. VII; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. VIII; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. IX; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. X; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1896 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. XI; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. XII; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Tennyson, Hallam; Alfred, Lord Tennyson: A Memoir by his son Vol. I; Dana Estes and Company; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Tennyson, Hallam; Alfred, Lord Tennyson: A Memoir by his son Vol. II; Dana Estes and Company; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Tennyson, Hallam; Alfred, Lord Tennyson: A Memoir by his son Vol. III; Dana Estes and Company; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Tennyson, Hallam; Alfred, Lord Tennyson: A Memoir by his son Vol. IV; Dana Estes and Company; Boston; 1897 (Box 20)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. I; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. II; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. II; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. IV; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. V; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Sue, Eugene; The Mysteries of Paris Vol. VI; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Literary Essays Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1864; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. I (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Literary Essays Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1870; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. II (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Literary Essays Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1870; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. III (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Literary Essays Vol. IV; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1871; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. IV (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Political Essays; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1871; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. V (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Literary and Political Addresses; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. VI (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; The Poetical Works Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. VII (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; The Poetical Works Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. VIII (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; The Divine Comedy of Dante Alighieri; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XI (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Life of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1891; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XII (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Life of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1891; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XIII (Box 21)
- Lowell, James Russell; Life of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1891; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XIV (Box 21)
- Fiske, John; Outlines of Cosmic Philosophy Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. I (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Outlines of Cosmic Philosophy Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. II (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Outlines of Cosmic Philosophy Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. III (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Outlines of Cosmic Philosophy Vol. IV; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. IV (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Myths and Mythmakers; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. V (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; The Unseen World and Other Essays; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. VI (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Excursions of an Evolutionist; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. VII (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; The Discovery of America Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Historical Writings of John Fiske Vol. I (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; The Discovery of America Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Historical Writings of John Fiske Vol. II (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; The Discovery of America Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Historical Writings of John Fiske Vol. III (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Old Virginia and Her Neighbours Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Historical Writings of John Fiske Vol. IV (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Old Virginia and Her Neighbours Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Historical Writings of John Fiske Vol. V (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Pages From an Old Volume of Life; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. VIII (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Medical Essays; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. IX (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Our Hundred Days in Europe; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. X (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Ralph Waldo Emerson, John Lothrop Motley; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. XI (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Poetical Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. XII (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Poetical Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. XIII (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Life and Letters of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. XIV (Box 22)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Life and Letters of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; 1892; The Works of Oliver Wendell Holmes Vol. XV (Box 22)
- Macaulay, Lord; The History of England: From the Accession of James the Second Vol. IV; Harper & Brothers; New York; 1879 (Box 22)
- Macaulay, Lord; The History of England: From the Accession of James the Second Vol. II; Harper & Brothers; New York; 1879 (Box 22)
- Bulwer, E.L.; The Student Vol. I; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 22)
- Bulwer, E.L.; The Student Vol. II; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 22)
- Fiske, John; Darwinism and Other Essays; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. VIII (Box 23)
- Fiske, John; Studies in Religion; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. IX (Box 23)
- Fiske, John; A Century of Science and Other Essays; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. X (Box 23)
- Fiske, John; The Mississippi Valley in the Civil War; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; The Miscellaneous Writings of John Fiske Vol. XI (Box 23)
- Rolfe, William J.; The Works of Alfred, Lord Tennyson Vol. I; Estes and Lauriat; Boston; 1895 (Box 23)
- Tyrwhitt, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Geoffrey Chaucer; Edward Moxon; London; 1851 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. I; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. II; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. III; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. IV; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. V; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. VI; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. VII; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. VIII; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1898 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. IX; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Vol. X; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 23)
- Stoddard, John L.; John L. Stoddard’s Lectures Supplementary Volume; Bach Brothers Co.; Boston; 1901 (Box 23)
- Irving, Washington; The Life and Voyages of Christopher Columbus Vol. III; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 24)
- Irving, Washington; Life of George Washington Vol. II; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 24)
- Irving, Washington; Life of George Washington Vol. III; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 24)
- Irving, Washington; Life of George Washington Vol. IV; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 24)
- Irving, Washington; Life of George Washington Vol. V; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 24)
- Arabian Tales Vol. I; Edinbrgh; 1792 (Box 24)
- Arabian Tales Vol. II; Edinbrgh; 1792 (Box 24)
- Arabian Tales Vol. III; Edinbrgh; 1792 (Box 24)
- Arabian Tales Vol. IV; Edinbrgh; 1792 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. I, 1000 A.D. – 1682; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. II, 1562 - 1733; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. III, 1745 - 1782; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. IV, 1784 - 1811; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. V, 1812 - 1828; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. VI, 1828 - 1840; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. VII, 1840 - 1860; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. VIII, 1860 - 1865; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. IX, 1865 - 1877; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- Halsey, Francis W.; Great Epochs in American History Vol. X, 1877 - 1911; Funk & Wagnalls Company; New York and London; 1912 (Box 24)
- The Poetical Works of Edmund Spencer Vol. I; William Pickering; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- The Poetical Works of Edmund Spencer Vol. II; William Pickering; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- The Poetical Works of Edmund Spencer Vol. III; William Pickering; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- The Poetical Works of Edmund Spencer Vol. IV; William Pickering; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- The Poetical Works of Edmund Spencer Vol. V; William Pickering; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. I; Saunders and Otley; London; 1836 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. II; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. III; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. IV; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. V; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. VI; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol.VIII; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Grimshawe, Rev. T.S.; The Life and Works of William Cowper Vol. VIII; Saunders and Otley; London; 1835 (Box 24)
- Poets and Poetry of the XIXth Century; Longman, Brown, Green, and Longmans; London; 1852 (Box 24)
- Francis, Philip; Horace Vol. I; A.J. Valpy; London; 1831 (Box 24)
- Francis, Philip; Horace Vol. II; A.J. Valpy; London; 1831 (Box 24)
- Dickens, Charles; The Pickwick Papers Vol. I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; The Pickwick Papers Vol. II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; The Pickwick Papers Vol. III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; The Pickwick Papers Vol. IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; Dombey and Son Vol. I; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; Dombey and Son Vol. II; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; Dombey and Son Vol. III; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Dickens, Charles; Dombey and Son Vol. IV; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 25)
- Irving, Washington; Mahomet Vol. I; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 25)